Privacy Policy

Last Updated: December 2018

Introduction

This Website is operated by eJournalPress, a division of Precision Computer Works, Inc. (the “Company”,“we”, “us”, or “our”). User privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy outlines our privacy practicesregarding information collected by this Website, ‐lists the types of data we collect, and explains how weuse and protect that data. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy so that you will understandboth our commitment to you and your privacy and how you can participate in that commitment.

BY VISITING OUR WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACYPOLICY AND CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONALLYIDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACYPOLICY. PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY TO GAIN AN UNDERSTANDINGOF OUR PRACTICES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THISPRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DISCONTINUE ALL USE OF THIS WEBSITE.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Customer Organization” shall mean any organization (publisher,publication, journal, society, organization, university, college, etc.) to which we provide Web servicesembodying this Website.

Gathering of Personally Identifiable Information

There are several ways we gather Personally Identifiable Information. We gather personal identifiableinformation (“Personally Identifiable Information”) such as full name, postal address, telephone number,e‐mail address, and other personally indentifying information when you register for an account at theWebsite. Your Personally Identifiable Information may also have been previously shared with us by theCustomer Organization. Additionally, you may also share Personally Identifiable Information with uswhile using features of this Website such as submitting or reviewing a manuscript, document or otherdata. Visitors can always refuse to supply Personally Identifiable Information, with the caveat that it willmay prevent them from using certain features of this Website.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We collect Non‐Personally Identifiable Information automatically when you visit this Website. Non‐Personally Identifiable Information is information that is not used nor intended to be used to personallyidentify an individual and is not associated with nor linked to Personally Identifiable Information. ThisNon‐Personally Identifiable Information we collect via the Website includes your Internet Protocoladdress, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your visit, and the web page you visitedimmediately prior to visiting the Website.

Cookies

We use Cookies on this Website. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to yourcomputer's web browser while you are viewing a website. Cookies are generally divided into essentialand non‐essential. The essential cookies are those necessary for providing the information requested bythe user. All the other cookies are considered non‐essential. Included here are identifiers used foranalytics, cookies from advertisers or third parties, including affiliates and those that identify a userwhen he returns to the website. We may use essential cookies to provide secure access to this Website.In accordance with GDPR and other privacy regulations, we request that our Customer Organizationsconfigure an “Opt‐In” question if they use any non‐essential cookies.

Aggregated statistics

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to this Website. We may display this informationpublicly or provide it to others. However, we do not disclose Personally Identifiable Information otherthan as described herein.

Ownership

We do not claim ownership of any of your Personally Identifiable Information. We collect and storePersonally Identifiable Information on our servers and computer networks as a data processor (“DataProcessor”) solely on behalf of our Customer Organizations (“Data Controllers”). All PersonallyIdentifiable Information is owned by the Customer Organization and may be accessed by the CustomerOrganization at any time.

THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT DESCRIBE OR GOVERN HOW THECUSTOMER ORGANIZATION MAY USE OR DISCLOSE ANY OF YOURPERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. WE DO NOT HAVE ANYINFORMATION CONCERNING HOW THE CUSTOMER ORGANIZATION MAY USEOR DISCLOSE ANY OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ANDYOU SHOULD CONSULT WITH THE CUSTOMER ORGANIZATION DIRECTLY FORINFORMATION CONCERNING HOW THEY WILL USE OR DISCLOSE YOURPERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.

How we use Personally Identifiable Information

 We use your Personally Identifiable Information to administer your account and provide servicesembodied by this Website, to send communications and administrative emails, and to respondto your inquiries.

 At the request of the Customer Organization, we will disclose your Personally IdentifiableInformation to the Customer Organization or transfer it to its other Data Processors.

 We may be required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if: (i) we believe it isreasonably necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, searchwarrant, etc.) or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) it would

potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit; (iii) it is otherwise necessary toprotect our rights or property; or (iv) it is necessary to protect the legal rights or property ofothers.

Use by Other Parties

All Personally Identifiable Information that you submit or otherwise make available while visiting theWebsite may be accessed and reviewed by any third party who has legitimate business reasons touse/access to the Website, including third parties who may have been authorized by the CustomerOrganization to perform certain tasks such as Administrators, Authors, Members of the Board of Editors,Editors, Associate Editors, Editors‐in‐Chief, Reviewers, Instructors, or Professors. In particular,Administrators generally will have the ability to access all of your Personally Identifiable Information.We cannot control how third parties who can access your Personally Identifiable Information may useyour Personally Identifiable Information and we have no means of tracking any use or disclosure of yourPersonally Identifiable Information by any such third party. If you believe that a third party hasunlawfully or improperly used or disclosed any of your Personally Identifiable Information, you shouldcontact the Customer Organization directly. ACCORDINGLY, YOU SHOULD EXERCISEGREAT CARE AND PRUDENCE BEFORE SUBMITTING OR MAKING AVAILABLEANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AT THIS WEBSITE.

Security

To protect the privacy of your Personally Identifiable Information, we employ industry‐standard controlsincluding physical access controls, Internet firewalls, anti‐virus software, and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)encryption.

Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage on the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.While we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot ensure or warrant thesecurity of any information you transmit to us.

Correcting or Updating Your Personally Identifiable Information

You can always update the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us via the“Modify Profile” link.

Governing Law / Arbitration

This Website is controlled and operated entirely within the United States. By using our Website, yousignify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy,please do not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information nor use this Website. This Privacy Policyand the use of the Website is soley governed by Maryland state law and United States federal law. Byuse of this Website, you agree to binding arbitration by JAMS (www.jamsadr.com) to resolve any claimrelated to the Website or this Privacy Policy. Users of the Website consent to the exclusive jurisdictionand venue of such arbitration as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes

concerning this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy and the notices outlined herein are not intended toand do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any third party.

Consent to Transfer

Users located outside the United States who submit information to this Website should be aware thatthe information they submit will be transferred to our servers located in the United States. Yoursubmission of information to the Website constitutes your consent to this transfer.

Links

This Website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for theprivacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site andto read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiableinformation. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

Minimum Age

This Website is not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. As such, this Website is notdirected at children under the age of 13 nor do we knowingly collect or maintain information fromchildren under the age of 13 on this Website. If you are under 13 years old, you are not authorized touse this Website.

Business transfers

If we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of businessor enter bankruptcy, information will be one of the assets that is likely to be transferred to, or acquiredby, a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and you consent to us transferringyour information to any acquirer and their continuing to use your Personally Identifiable Information asset forth in this policy.

Privacy policy changes

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and at our sole discretion. We encourage visitorsto frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site afterany change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Contacting Us

We can be contacted by mail:

Privacy OfficerPrecision Computer Works, Inc.5508 Greentree RoadBethesda, MD 20817 USA
